Finding Aid for the Edward C. Weber Papers, 1949-2005
Edward C. Weber Papers
- Correspondence
  - Sasquatch Books (reference: IWW photos book on Washington state history) (Box 41)
  - Satter, Mark J. (reference: Haymarket trial transcripts) (Box 41)
  - Savage, Ronald J. (reference: Father Thomas J. Haggerty) (Box 41)
  - Sayles, Alan (reference: American anarchism) (Box 41)
  - Scanlan, Eleanor H. (reference: biographical info for Michigan Index to Labor Union Periodicals) (Box 41)
  - Scarafoni, Deborah (Box 41)
  - Schaffer, Constance (Box 41)
  - Schaber, Ralph F. (re: donation of Truth Seeker and other freethought publications) (Box 41)
  - Schapsmeier, Walter (reference: Walter Lippmann) (Box 41)
  - Scharnau, Ralph W. (reference: native American anarchism; Josiah Warren) (Box 41)
  - Scheips, Paul J. (reference: Knights of Labor song) (Box 41)
  - Schild, Jochen (reference: political rhetoric of the right and left in the USA since 1955) (Box 41)
  - Schindehuette, Reinhard M. (reference: early AFL and its affiliated unions) (Box 41)
  - Schlagenhauff, Annette (reference: ideas on art and revolution in France in the 1920s) (Box 41)
  - Schlichter, Robert (re: subscriptions to his publications Report and Review; May Day!) (Box 41)
  - Schmaltz, William (reference: George Lincoln Rockwell; American Nazi Party) (Box 41)
  - Schmu, Ma (reference: Max Nettlau; Chinese translation of Godwin’s On Property; Sifo) (Box 41)
  - Schniderman, Saul (re: Talkin’ Union; donation of labor materials) (Box 41)
  - Schoeps, Julius H. (reference: Ferdinand Freiligrath; Karl Heinzen) (Box 41)
  - Schoffman, Stuart (reference: Benjamin Tucker) (Box 41)
  - Scholarly Resources, Inc. (Box 41)
  - Scholastic, Inc. (reference: IWW; Wesley Everest; Ricardo Flores Magon) (Box 41)
  - Scholten, Pat (reference: Mother Jones; Ella Reeve Bloor; Elizabeth Gurley Flynn; Rose Schneiderman; Agnes Nestor) (Box 41)
  - School of Living (Box 41)
  - School Stopper’s Textbook (Box 41)
  - Schuck, Robert (Box 41)
  - Schultz, Gretchen (Box 41)
  - Schulze, David (reference: IWW and unemployed in Western Canada in 1913-14) (Box 41)
  - Schwantes, Carlos A. (reference: anarchist literature in the Pacific Northwest; Jacob Coxey) (Box 41)
  - Schwarz, Bob (reference: Malcolm X appearance in Michigan) (Box 42)
  - Schwertz, Dr. Joseph S., Sr. (re: ECW request for copy of High School Reform) (Box 42)
  - Schwoegler, Stephen J. (reference: Frank Little) (Box 42)
  - Scott, Laurence (Box 42)
  - Scottish Homosexual Rights Group (Box 42)
  - Scottish Lesbian Feminists (re: Red Herring) (Box 42)
  - Screw (New York) (Box 42)
  - Searles, Richard (reference: Joseph and Laurance Labadie’s writings) (Box 42)
  - Sears, Hal D. (reference: Moses and Lillian Harman; Edwin C. Walker) (Box 42)
  - Sechaba Publications (African National Congress) (Box 42)
  - Sébastien, Jean (reference: microfilm of MacKnight Black’s poetry) (Box 42)
  - See Sharp Press (donation of materials; wants copy of Fabbri's "Bourgeois Influences on Anarchism") (Box 42)
  - Seeger, Peggy (re: New City Songster) (Box 42)
  - Seiatel (Buenos Aires, Argentina) (Box 42)
  - Seidler, Murray (reference: Norman Thomas; New America) (Box 42)
  - Sekyere, Festus Owusu (Ghana) (Box 42)
  - Self Management Group of Western Australia (formerly The West Australian Anarchist Federation) (Box 42)
  - Sell, Evelyn (reference: Socialist Workers Party 1968 election campaign) (Box 42)
  - Sellars, Nigel (reference: IWW in Oklahoma) (Box 42)
  - Selma Inter-religious Project (Box 42)
  - Selmer, Kristin (Box 42)
  - Selth, Jeff (reference: contemporary commune, nudism, sexual freedom movement, no reply) (Box 42)
  - Selvin, David F. (reference: photographs of Haywood and Debs for book on American labor leaders) (Box 42)
  - Senza, Patria (Box 42)
  - Seme Anarchico (Italy) (Box 42)
  - Serendipity Books (re: purchase of Free Society) (Box 42)
  - Seretan, L. Glen (reference: Daniel DeLeon; Socialist Labor Party; etc.) (Box 42)
  - Serlin, David (reference: Charles Ashleigh; Claude McKay; William Rollins, Jr.) (Box 42)
  - Seven Days (New York) (Box 42)
  - Seven Seas Press (Box 42)
  - Shackleford, Martin (re: donation of book on Kennedy assassination) (Box 42)
  - Shadley, Bob (reference: communes in the United States) (Box 42)
  - Shah, Nayan (reference: anti-Chinese legislation; white labor attitudes toward Chinese workers in the U.S.; Agnes Inglis’s settlement work) (Box 42)
  - Shanahan, Bill (reference: Liberty, Benjamin Tucker; letter from ECW about visit to Bubbling Waters) (Box 42)
  - Shanks, Phil (reference: Songs of the Wobblies; IWW) (Box 42)
  - Shanley, R.V. (reference: Spanish Civil War) (Box 42)
  - Shapiro, Chaim (re: donation of radical pamphlets from W.A.N. Collier) (Box 42)
  - Shapiro, Herbert (reference: Walter Drew; Lincoln Steffens; Progressive Movement) (Box 42)
  - Sharbach, Sarah (reference: Modern School Magazine; Louise Olivereau) (Box 42)
  - Sharma, Om P. (Box 42)
  - Sharp, Kathleen (reference: women in radical groups 1890-1920) (Box 42)
  - Shaw, Alan (Box 42)
  - Shaw, Bruno (reference: Robert LaFollette; Socialist Party platform of 1924; Prohibition Party) (Box 42)
  - Shaver, Joe (reference: offer of anarchist materials) (Box 42)
  - Shea, Robert (re: sending LC copies of No Governor) (Box 42)
  - Sheaffer, Louis (reference: Charles Ashleigh; Terence Carlin; Hippolyte Havel) (Box 42)
  - Sheldon, John (reference: “The Joe Hill Case” by James O. Morris) (Box 42)
  - Shelby, Deborah (reference: survey of archives housing lesbian and gay materials) (Box 42)
  - Sher, Laurel (reference: Alternatives in Print) (Box 42)
  - Sherward, Diane (reference: Laurance Labadie Papers) (Box 42)
  - Shiley, James (Box 42)
  - Shilts, Randy (reference: homosexual experience in the military) (Box 42)
  - Shively, Charles (reference: homosexual writers and literary figures) (Box 42)
  - Shor, Francis (reference: Joseph Cohen; Sunrise Farm Cooperative) (Box 42)
  - Shore, Elliott (reference: Allan Benson; Appeal to Reason; Debs scrapbooks) (Box 42)
  - Sibley, Abigail (reference: Teacher’s International Review) (Box 42)
  - Sicherman, Barbara (reference: ACPFB Papers; Alice Hamilton) (Box 42)
  - Sides, Ann B. (reference: William Buwalda who attended a speech by Emma Goldman) (Box 42)
  - Silberman, Ellen G. (reference: permission to use IWW image in Invisible America) (Box 42)
  - Silver, Madeline (reference: Attitudes Toward Homosexuality Scales; Lon Nungesser) (Box 42)
  - Silverman, Max (reference: silver movement; monetary reform) (Box 42)
  - Silverman, Shulman & Baker, P.C. (reference: thanks for use of photograph for European history examination) (Box 42)
  - Sinclair, Glenn (reference: Canadian student activist organizations; radical Canadiana) (Box 42)
  - Singerman, Robert (anti-Semitism; anti-Jewish materials in LC) (Box 42)
  - Singham, Nancy L. (reference: publishing activities of socialist and communist parties) (Box 42)
  - Sipe, Gregory (reference: general inquiry about anarchist holdings in LC) (Box 42)
  - Sipapu (Evanston, IL) (Box 42)
  - Siren Newsletter (Chicago, IL) (Box 42)
  - Sitcoff, Harvard (reference: Civil Rights Movement in the 1940s) (Box 42)
  - Situationist International (New York) (Box 42)
  - Skyhorse/Mohawk Offense/Defense Committee (Box 42)
  - Slate (Berkeley, CA) (Box 42)
  - Slatter, John (reference: Peter Kropotkin) (Box 42)
  - Slawikowski, John (re: compiling bibliography on American anarchism) (Box 43)
  - Slight, Joseph (Box 43)
  - Sloothak, Mike (re: trading of duplicates with Gerber Hart Library) (Box 43)
  - Sluder, Claude L. (reference: music of Josiah Warren; New Harmony) (Box 43)
  - Smith, Anthony T. (re: Alliance for Equal Opportunity; homosexual prisoner rights at Angola and other U.S. prisons) (Box 43)
  - Smith, David (reference: general inquiry regarding LC holdings on Trotskyism and Fourth International) (Box 43)
  - Smith, Gibbs M. (reference: Joe Hill; Industrial Worker; IWW) (Box 43)
  - Smith, Jessie Carney (reference: photo of Lucy Parsons for publication on Notable Black Women) (Box 43)
  - Smith, Robert W. (reference: farmers’ crusade of the 1890s; Populist Movement) (Box 43)
  - Smith, W. T. (reference: IWWs in the Kuzbas; Russia) (Box 43)
  - Smithsonian Institution (reference: Josiah Warren; Charles Coffin Jewett; John Punchard Jewett) (Box 43)
  - Smolinski, Gerald K. (reference: IWW report by Howard Scott) (Box 43)
  - Smyrna Press (re: purchase of Detroit, I Do Mind Dying) (Box 43)
  - Snow, Richard (reference: SDS; SSOC) (Box 43)
  - Snowberger, Garnet (re: offer of two issues of Truth Seeker from 1965) (Box 43)
  - Snyder, Robert (reference: Tin Can Tourists) (Box 43)
  - Social Democrats, USA (Box 43)
  - Social Protest Project, UC Berkeley (Box 43)
  - Sociale Diffusion (Montréal, Canada) (Box 43)
  - Socialist Affairs (London, England) (Box 43)
  - Socialist Forum (New York) (Box 43)
  - Socialist Labor Party (re: donation of SLP publications) (Box 43)
  - Socialist Labour League (London) (Box 43)
  - Socialist Party of Michigan (Box 43)
  - Socialist Party USA (Box 43)
  - Socialist Reconstruction (New York) (Box 43)
  - Socialist Workers 1976 California Campaign (Box 43)
  - Socialist Workers Party (Box 43)
  - Society for the Protection of Personal Privileges (Tel Aviv, Israel) (Box 43)
  - Society of Lesbian and Gay Anthropologists (SOLGA) (Box 43)
  - Sol III (Philadelphia, PA) (Box 43)
  - Soldiers of the Cross (Englewood, CO) (Box 43)
  - Solé, M. Angels (re: offer to sell clandestine materials from Francoist Spain) (Box 43)
  - Solidarite Ouvriere (France) (reply from IWW regarding CNT in Spain) (Box 43)
  - Solidarity (Aberdeen) (Box 43)
  - Solidarity (London) (Box 43)
  - Solidarity (North London) (Box 43)
  - Solidarity (South London) (Box 43)
  - Solidarity Newsletter (Philadelphia, PA) (Box 43)
  - Solidarity Bookshop (Chicago) (Box 43)
  - Solomon, Mark (re: purchase of Harrington Collection of Seven Seas Books) (Box 43)
  - Solvick, Stanley D. (Reuther Library) (reference: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn recording; New America Movment) (Box 43)
  - Sonn, Richard (reference: European anarchism) (Box 43)
  - Sonn, William J. (reference: European anarchist movement) (Box 43)
  - Sons of Liberty (Hollywood, CA) (Box 43)
  - Soriano, Scott (reference: Voltairine de Cleyre) (Box 43)
  - Sosnik, Nancy (re: CSPAN School Bus program) (Box 43)
  - Souchy, Augustin (reference: Erich Mühsam) (Box 43)
  - Source (Washington DC) (Box 43)
  - South Slovenian Socialist Labor Federation (Cleveland, OH) (re: donation of Radnicka Borba) (Box 43)
  - Southern Africa (New York) (Box 43)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (Atlanta) (Box 43)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund (Box 43)
  - Southern Gay Liberator (Delray Beach, FL) (Box 43)
  - Southern Libertarian Messenger (Atlanta) (Box 43)
  - Southern Libertarian Review (Arlington, VA) (Box 43)
  - Southern Regional Council (Atlanta) (Box 43)
  - Southern Rural Research Project (Selma, AL) (Box 43)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee (Nashville, TN) (Box 43)
  - Southwest Intergroup Relations Council (Austin, TX) (Box 43)
  - Southwick, Leslie (reference: James B. Weaver; B.J. Chambers; Greenback Party) (Box 43)
  - Sozialistisches Osteuropakomitee (Hamburg, Germany) (Box 43)
  - Space City (Houston, TX) (Box 43)
  - Spadafore, Joseph (re: various biographical and intellectual subjects) (Italian-American anarchist) (Box 43)
  - Spady, James (reference: Negro-Caucasian Club; Oakley Johnson; Erdmann Beynon) (Box 43)
  - Spalek, John M. (re: Internationale wissenschaftliche Korrespondenz zur Geschichte der Deutschen Arbeiterbewegung) (Box 43)
  - Spahn, Theodore (reference: Madalyn Murray O’Hair; Ayn Rand) (Box 43)
  - Spanish Information Network (Box 43)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid, Inc. (Box 43)
  - Spark, The (Progressive Labor Movement - Berkeley) (Box 43)
  - Spark, The (Baltimore; Detroit) (Box 43)
  - Spartacist, The (New York) (Box 43)
  - Spartacus International Ltd. (Amsterdam) (Pan Magazine) (Box 43)
  - Speak Out (Detroit) (Box 43)
  - Spearhead (London) (Box 43)
  - Special Operations Research Center (reference: Black Nationalism) (Box 44)
  - Spectacular Times (London) (Box 44)
  - Spectator, The (Berkeley, CA) (Box 44)
  - Spectator, The (Bloomington, IN) (Box 44)
  - Spectre (Ann Arbor) (Box 44)
  - Spectrum (London) (Box 44)
  - Spencer, Lisa (donation of The Black Rose) (Box 44)
  - Spider Magazine (Oakland, CA) (Box 44)
  - Spiegelman, Willard (reference: gay journalism) (Box 44)
  - Spitze, Glenna D. (reference: Voltairine de Cleyre; Emma Goldman) (Box 44)
  - Spokesman, The (Bertrand Russell’s publication) (Nottingham, England) (Box 44)
  - Spokeswoman, The (Chicago, IL) (Box 44)
  - Spotlight on South Africa (see: Sechaba Publications) (Box 44)
  - Sprague, Jo (reference: speeches by or about women) (Box 44)
  - Sprout, Richard (re: donation of anarchist materials) (Box 44)
  - Sprout, The (Denver, CO) (Box 44)
  - Spurlock, John (reference: photographs for book on Free Love Movement) (Box 44)
  - Sputnik (English edition) (Box 44)
  - Square (Westwood Village Square, West Los Angeles, CA) (Box 44)
  - Staebler, Neil (re: T. Casey Brennan) (Box 44)
  - Stand Up (Eugene, OR) (Box 44)
  - Stangis, Pat (Box 44)
  - Starring, Robert (Box 44)
  - State Historical Society of Wisconsin (Jim Danky) (Box 44)
  - State University of New York at Stony Brook (reference: Oakley Johnson materials in LC) 1 of 2 (Box 44)
  - State University of New York at Stony Brook (re: purchase of previously owned LC pamphlet) 2 of 2 (Box 44)
  - Statecraft (Alexandria, VA) (Box 44)
  - Statements (Berkeley, CA) (Box 44)
  - Stavis, Barrie (reference: Joe Hill, IWW, White Pine Shorty) (Box 44)
  - Steele, Richard W. (reference: U.S government treatment of aliens during 1938-1945; ACPFB) (Box 44)
  - Steichman, Kate R. (re: donation of books) (Box 44)
  - Steid, Charles (reference: bibliography of bisexuality) (Box 44)
  - Stein, Gordon (freethought; ethnic anti-clerical; anti-religious publications and movements) (Box 44)
  - Stein, Gordon (estate of) (re: purchase of books) (Box 44)
  - Stein, Harry (reference: Lincoln Steffens) (Box 44)
  - Stelle Letter (Stelle, IL) (Box 44)
  - Stemer, Stella Anne (Box 44)
  - Stephens, Michael P. (reference: bibliography of Charles H. Kerr Co. publications) (Box 44)
  - Stern, Madeleine B. (reference: biography of Stephen Pearl Andrews) (Box 44)
  - Stern, Der (Hamburg, Germany) (Box 44)
  - Stevens, David (reference: Julia Orvis; writing biography of John Montgomery Ward) (Box 44)
  - Stevenson, Billie Jean (reference: dissertation on ideology of American anarchism in late 19th century) (Box 44)
  - Stewart, Mrs. M. V. (reference: Emma Goldman) (Box 44)
  - Stewas, R.C. (Box 44)
  - Stich, Klaus Peter (reference: John H. Mackay and George Schumm correspondence) (Box 44)
  - Stoddard, Richard (book dealer) (Box 44)
  - Stoddard, Roger E. (re: Chuck Dodson; LC holdings on sexual freedom) (Box 44)
  - Stoffle, Carla (re: purchases of materials for LC) (Box 44)
  - Stoffle, Carla (re: purchases of materials for LC) (Box 44)
  - Stop the War (re: subscription to Revelator) (Box 44)
  - Story, Ian (Box 44)
  - Stowasser, Horst (re: subscription to Schwarze Tinte) (Box 44)
  - Stowe, Leland (Box 44)
  - Straight Creek Journal (Denver, CO) (Box 44)
  - Strassberg, Jerome (reference: Emma Goldman) (Box 44)
  - Street, Richard (reference: California farm workers) (Box 44)
  - Strong, Anna Louise (letter from ECW) (Box 44)
  - Strong, David (Box 45)
  - Strottman, Jeff (English language anarchist serials; anarchist self-education) (Box 45)
  - Struggle (Detroit, MI) (Box 45)
  - Struggle Continues, The (London, England) (Box 45)
  - Struik, Dirk J. (reference: John Francis Bray) (Box 45)
  - Stucky, Mrs. Sol (reference: Victor Berger) (Box 45)
  - Student Federalist (Washington DC) (Box 45)
  - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 45)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee (SNCC) (Box 45)
  - Student Peace Union Bulletin (New York) (Box 45)
  - Student Press Law Center (letter from ECW) (Box 45)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (Box 45)
  - Studies on the Left (New York) (Box 45)
  - Suagr, Theresa J. (reference: the Dearborn Colony) (Box 45)
  - Subversity (York, England) (Box 45)
  - Sugiarto, Stephanus E. (wants information about local gay newspapers) (Box 45)
  - Sullivan, Mark (reference: Laurance Labadie; Benjamin Tucker) (Box 45)
  - Sullivan, William A. (reference: Bill Haywood; WFM; strikes in copper mines of northern Michigan) (Box 45)
  - Summerfeld, Mary Ellen (reference: Black Panther newspaper) (Box 45)
  - Summers, Charles (Box 45)
  - Summers, Claude J. (re: his article on Maurice) (Box 45)
  - Sun Pub. Co. (Albuquerque, NM) (Box 45)
  - Sun (Detroit, Ann Arbor) (Box 45)
  - Sun Reporter (San Francisco) (Box 45)
  - Sundergeld, Hans (reference: Francisco Ferrer; Modern School) (Box 45)
  - Survival of American Indians Assn. (Tacoma, WA) (Box 45)
  - Survival Network Information Center (New Orleans, LA) (Box 45)
  - Suttles, Shirley (reference: IWW; Walker Smith; Centralia) (Box 45)
  - Sutton, Anthony C. (reference: Francis Tandy; Free Competition) (Box 45)
  - Sveriges Arbetares Centralorganisation (SAC) (Stockholm, Sweden) (Box 45)
  - Swados, Harvey (re: negative statement about the Labadie Collection) (Box 45)
  - Swallow, Mrs. Marvin R. (reference: Spanish language anarchist periodicals of the 1930s) (Box 45)
  - Swancara, Frank (re: purchase of issues of The Truth Seeker) (Box 45)
  - Swanson, Dorothy (Head Librarian, Tamiment Library) (reference: Independent Socialist Mimeographica) (Box 45)
  - Swann Galleries, Inc. (Box 45)
  - Swarr, Amanda (reference: LGBT general info) (Box 45)
  - Swarts, Valerie R. (reference: women’s suffrage movement) (Box 45)
  - Swedish Pioneer Historical Quarterly (reference: portrait of Joe Hill) (Box 45)
  - Sweeny (Oakville, Ontario) (Box 45)
  - Swinging Coq (contains documents of confiscation by U.S. for obscenity) (Box 45)
  - Sykore, George and Jane (Box 45)
  - Sylvester & Orphanos (Booksellers) (Box 45)
  - Syndicalist Workers Federation (England) (Box 45)
  - Synergistic Press (Box 45)
  - Synthesis (San Pedro, CA) (Box 45)
  - Syracuse University Press (reference: photographs of Bill Haywood, etc.) (Box 45)
  - Taconic Foundation, Inc. (Box 45)
  - Tactics (Arlington, VA) (Box 45)
  - Taft, Mrs. Philip (re: donation of correspondence between Inglis and Philip Taft about Bray) (Box 45)
  - Take Over (Madison, WI) (Box 45)
  - Takeda, Yoshimi (Box 45)
  - Talalay, Kathy (reference: Phillippa Schuyler) (Box 45)
  - Talkin’ Union (re: donation of materials to LC) (Box 45)
  - Tamarkin, Stanley R. (reference: Rose Pastor Stokes) (Box 45)
  - Tamiment Institute Library (various correspondence 1961-1996) (Box 46)
  - Tampa Red & Black (Tampa, FL) (Box 46)
  - Tamtam (Vienna, Austria) (includes letter from ECW about LGBT matters) (Box 46)
  - Tannen, Holly (Box 46)
  - Tap (New York, NY) (Box 46)
  - Tarver, John (reference: lumber industry in the Trans-Mississippi South from 1880-1920) (Box 46)
  - Tasmanian Gay and Lesbian Rights Group (Tasmania, Australia) (Box 46)
  - Tax, Meredith (reference: radical women, 1890-1920) (Box 46)
  - Taylor, Mrs. Allen (offer to sell Helen Augur book with letters) (Box 46)
  - Taylor, Sue D. (reference: Ellis Island Anarchist Weekly) (Box 46)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union (Cleveland, OH) (Box 46)
  - Technocracy, Inc. (Rushland, PA) (Box 46)
  - Tekla, Tad (re: donation of materials to LC) (Box 46)
  - Temple University, Contemporary Culture Center (Box 46)
  - Tercer Sol Bookstore, El (Box 46)
  - Terra Lliure (Paris, France) (Box 46)
  - Terrorism and Political Violence (London) (Box 46)
  - Terrorism Research Centre (Cape Town, South Africa) (reference: bombing of Army Math Research Center in Madison, WI, 1970) (Box 46)
  - Texas Observer (Austin, TX) (Box 46)
  - Theisen, James (reference: Ralph Chaplin poem, “Adam Revisits Paradise”) (Box 46)
  - Third World Reports (London) (Box 46)
  - This Magazine (Toronto) (Box 46)
  - Thomas, Hulan G. (reference: Highlander Folk School) (Box 46)
  - Thomas, Joan (widow of Ammon Hennacy; many letters from ECW) (Box 46)
  - Thomas, Roy R. (reference: Louis Post) (Box 46)
  - Thompson, Arthur W. (reference: Russian Revolution of 1905) (Box 46)
  - Thompson, Lawrence S. (reference: Bloody Monday riot in Louisville, KY in 1855) (Box 46)
  - Thompson, William (Box 46)
  - Thomson, George C. (re: his book The Quest for Truth about Kennedy assassination) (Box 46)
  - Thorne, Ahrne (reference: Sacco & Vanzetti commemorative flyer) (Box 46)
  - Thorne, Paula (re: donation of materials to LC; many letters between her and ECW) (Box 46)
  - Thorsen, Niels (reference: Laurence Gronlund/Peter Lofgreen) (Box 46)
  - Thornton, Jerry (Box 46)
  - Thunder (Peoples Progressive Party) (Box 46)
  - Thunder and Lightning (National White American Party) (Olympia, WA) (Box 46)
  - Thunderbolt, The (Marietta, GA) (Box 46)
  - Thurner, Arthur W. (reference: Michigan copper miner’s strike of 1913-1914) (Box 46)
  - Thwin, Tun (Box 46)
  - Tierra y Libertad (Mexico) (Box 46)
  - Tietjen, Randall (reference: Clarence Darrow—includes publication permission from Darrow family) (Box 46)
  - Timberlake, Charles E. (reference: American communes in Russia in the 1920s and 30s) (Box 46)
  - Timberlane Press (Box 46)
  - Times Change Press (Box 46)
  - Timko, Mike (reference: Josiah Warren) (Box 46)
  - Tirabassi, Maddalena (reference: Italian-American anti-fascism, 1918-1941) (Box 46)
  - Tobin, Michael (re: Hapotoc; donation of The Vision Our Time Demands) (Box 46)
  - Todd, Alden (re: Laurence Todd’s memoir) (Box 46)
  - Tomato Publications (Box 46)
  - Tonelli, Lisa (reference: Barnet Braverman) (Box 46)
  - Tonkovich, Andrew (reference: American anarchism; de Cleyre; Berkman; Brown) (Box 46)
  - Torch, The (Revolutionary Socialist League, Highland Park, MI) (Box 46)
  - Tormey, James J. (re: The Papers of Betty Gannett) (Box 47)
  - Toronto Anarchist Group (Box 47)
  - Toronto Libertarian and Anarchist Group (Box 47)
  - Tortorelli, Federico (reference: Josiah Warren; Stephen Pearl Andrews) (Box 47)
  - Touzot, Jean (jobber) (Box 47)
  - Towanda Public Library (reference: want to borrow specific IWW and WFM materials) (Box 47)
  - Toy, Eckard V. Jr. (reference: KKK; fascist groups; Silver Shirts; neo-Nazis; American Bund, etc.) (Box 47)
  - Trans-Love Energies (Detroit, MI) (Box 47)
  - Transformation (Toronto, Ontario) (Box 47)
  - Transition (Accra, Ghana) (Box 47)
  - Trautmann, Frederick (reference: Johann Most) (Box 47)
  - Travailleurs Deportes et Refractaires (Brussels) (Box 47)
  - Tribune (London) (Box 47)
  - Tri-Continental Information Center (New York) (Box 47)
  - Tri-Continental Magazine (Havana, Cuba) (Box 47)
  - Tripp, Anne H. (reference: Agnes Inglis; IWW) (Box 47)
  - Tripp, Paivi (reference: anarchist movement in Chicago in the 1880s; Haymarket) (Box 47)
  - Trud! (New Jersey) (Box 47)
  - Trueblood, Chris ( The Gay Marxist- Manchester, England; includes info about gay groups in U.S.) (Box 47)
  - Truth (Oak Park, IL) (Trotskyists) (Box 47)
  - Truth, The (Danbury, NH) (Box 47)
  - Truth Seeker, The (San Diego, CA) (Box 47)
  - Tsang, Daniel (LGBT serials in the Labadie Collection) (Box 47)
  - Tsusuki, Chughichi (reference: Eleanor and Edward Aveling-letter missing from LC) (Box 47)
  - Tuchman, Arleen (reference: Dr. Marie Elizabeth Zakrzewska; Karl Heinzen) (Box 47)
  - Tucker, Tommy (reference: 1912 Lawrence textile strike) (Box 47)
  - Tugas, Patrica (Ellis) (re: CSPAN program on LC) (Box 47)
  - Tulane University (re: Covington Hall; “Labor Struggles in the Deep South”) (Box 47)
  - Turbow, Will (former LC student assistant) (Box 47)